Guide to the University Photography records, [ca.1989-2001]
University Photography records,
- Faculty and staff
  - N-P
    - Noble, Lucinda, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 195)
    - Noden, Malcolm, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Nolan, Bob, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Norkus, Greg, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Negatives included. Item from 1996 is a negative of an unnamed woman in what looks like the Johnson Museum
    - Norton, Mary Beth, 1988-2003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Novakovic, Andrew, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Nowicki, Margaret, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Noy, Noa, 1997-2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Noyes Jr., Jansen, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Nozelle, John, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Nozick, Linda, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Nozzolia, Michael, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Nye, Bill, 1996-2003 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Nyerkan, Jennifer, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Obendorf, Ralph, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Ober, Chris, 1997-2003 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Oberly, Gene, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Obern, Catheryn, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Oblak, Janice, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - O'Brien, Tim, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - O'Connor, Tom, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Odak, Perry, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Ohadike, Don, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - O'Hart, Ted, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Oja, Shambhu, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Okihiro, Gary, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Olbricht, William, 1993-2002 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Olguin, Ben, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Oliver, Amy, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Olpadwala, Porus, 1994-1998 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Olson, Christine, 1990-1997 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      Two photos undated. Photocopy included
    - Olson, Jeff, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Oltenacu, P.A., Undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Ondrako, Ed, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - O'Neil, Kathleen, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Oppenheim, Emia, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Opperman, Mary, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Orear, Jay, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Orlov, Yuri, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - O'Rourke, Thomas, 1990-2003 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Ortiz, Ana, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Osborn, Agda, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Osgood, Russell, 1988-1998 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Osika, Dennis, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Ostrander, Ed, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Owens, Thomas, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Padamsee, Hasan, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Paddock, Ken, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Page, Greg, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Palmer, Larry, 1983-1995 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Papapietro, Patti, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Papoulia, Katerina, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Parker, Jeffrey, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Parker, Robert, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Parks, John, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Parks, Ron, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Parks, Thomas, 1986-1996 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Parrot, Andrea, 1990-1997 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      Undated negatives and photographs included
    - Parsons, Louise, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Paul, Robert, 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Paul, Terry, 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Peckarsky, Bobby, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Pederson, Ann, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Pell, Alice, 1990-2001 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Pelletier, David, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Pendergast, Tim, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Penner, Richard, 1994-1998 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Pepe, Jean, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Peraino, Judith, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Perez, Pedro, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Peter, George, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Peters, Elizabeth, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Peters, Harriet, 1993-2001 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Peters, Joe, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Peterson, Randall, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Petrina, Petru, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Petrovic, Martin, 1991-1998 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Pezzotti, Guiseppe, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Phemister, Robert, 1985-1994 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Philips, Lance, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Philips, Laura, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Phillips, William E., 1997 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Phoenix, Leigh, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Pichenik, Alex, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Piedra, Jose, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Pike, Allen, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Pike, Linda, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Piliero, Susan, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Pillemer, Karl, 1990-2001 (Box 9, Folder 88)
      Items from 2001 are a photocopy and an email
    - Pimentel, David, 1992-2002 (Box 9, Folder 89)
      Negatives and an undated photo of Marcia Pimentel included.
    - Pinch, Trevor, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Pingali, Keshav, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Plaisted, Bob, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Plater, Terry, 1994-1999 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Plfeiderer, John, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Poe, Ann Sampson, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Poe, Greg, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Pohl, Robert, 1984-1999 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Polachek, Dora, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Polenberg, Richard, 1981-2001 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Poleskie, Steve, 1973-1990 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Pollack, Lois, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Pollak, John, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Pollock, Clifford, 1988-2002 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Pond, Steven, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Pope, Stephen, 1998-2002 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Poppensiek, George C., 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 106)
      Descriptions on the back of two photographs
    - Porte, Joel, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 107)
      Undated photocopy included
    - Porter, Keith, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Porter, Roosevelt, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Posner, George, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Potter, Earl, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Povinelli, Elizabeth, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Powell, R. Steven, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Power, Alison, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Powers, David, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Powers, Erika, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Powers, Jacquie, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Prabhakar, Arati, Undated (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Pretty, Jules, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 119)
      Negatives with descriptions only
    - Price, David, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Protter, Philip, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Pryor, Keith, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Pucik, Vladimir, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Putnam, David, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Q-R
    - Quaas, R.L., Undated (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Quest, James, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Quigley, Maureen, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Quirk, Susan, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Rabkin, Jeremy, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Racine, Anita, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Radke, Celia, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Raffensberger, Ed, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Rainsford, Peter, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Rakow, Don, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Ramage, Andrew, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Ramakrishna, Ravi, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - Ramin, Richard M., 1971-1992; ZD-88 (Box 9, Folder 137)
      Press releases, undated photographs, and undated zip disk included
    - Rand, Richard, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Randel, Don, 1991-1998 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Rasmussen, Kathleen, 1987-1998 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Rathbun, Lynn, 1989-1997 (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - Rauker, Marty, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Raver, Cybele, 1994-1999 (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - Rawson, Richard, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - Raynor, Bruce, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Rayor, Linda, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - Rebuhn, William, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - Redden, Timothy, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 148)
    - Redlin, Michael, 1991-1998 (Box 9, Folder 149)
    - Reeve, H. Kern, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 150)
    - Reeve, Janet, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 151)
    - Regan, Dennis, 1993-2001 (Box 9, Folder 152)
    - Regan, Elizabeth, 1986-1998 (Box 9, Folder 153)
    - Regenstein, Joe, 1992-2001 (Box 9, Folder 154)
    - Rehkngler, Carole, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 155)
    - Reich, Robert B., 1994 (Box 9, Folder 156)
    - Reichenbach, Inge, 1992-2001 (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - Reid, Doug, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 158)
    - Rendell, Michael, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - Rendsburg, Gary, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - Renegar, James, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 161)
    - Reno, Janet, 1993-2003 (Box 9, Folder 162)
    - Renwick, J. Alan, 1995-2001 (Box 9, Folder 163)
      One set of photographs undated. Negatives and a photocopy included
    - Reppy, Judith, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Reps, John, 1985-1998 (Box 9, Folder 165)
    - Resler, Edwin, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 166)
    - Reynolds, Dennis, 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 167)
    - Reynolds, Eleanor, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 168)
    - Reynolds, YokeSan, 1996-2001 (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - Rhodes, Frank, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Rhodes, Mary, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - Rhodin, Thor, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 172)
    - Ricciuti, Henry, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Negatives and an undated photograph enclosed
    - Richard, Tom, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Richards, Ann, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Richardson, Robert, 1978-1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Richardson, Ruth, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Richmond, Bonnie, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Rider, Teresa, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Riley, Richard W., Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Ripple, Richard, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Rivchin, Marilyn, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Rizvi, Syed, 1989-1994 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Roberson, Quinetta, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Roberts, Don, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Roberts, E.F., 1971-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Roberts, Jeffrey, 1993-1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Robertson, David, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Robertson, Martha, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Robertson, Steve, 1995-2000 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Robinson, Frank, 1992-2002 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Robinson, Jean, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Robinson, Kenneth, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Robinson, Larry, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Robinson, Laurie, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Rodriguez, Eloy, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Rodriguez, Eunice, 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Roe, Daphne, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Rogers, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Rogers, Fred, 1992-1999 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Rosen, Bill, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Rosenbaum, Toni, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Rosenberg, Edgar, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Rosenberg, Leah, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Rosenberry, Lorraine, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Rossi, Faust, 1971-2000 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Rossiter, Margaret, 1989-1997 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Roth, Nelson, 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Roundy, Robin, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Rovers, Adriana, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Rugina, Radu, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Ruhe, Brian, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Ruina, David, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Ruiz-Quintinella, Antonio, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Ruoff, Arthur, 1966-1998 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      Negatives and some photograph descriptions included. One photograph undated
    - Rushmore, Cindy, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Rushmore, Judy, 1992-1997 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Russell, James, Undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
      Undated negative and photograph included
    - Russell, Nerissa, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Ryan, Kathleen, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Rypisi, Candace, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - S-T
    - Sachse, Wolfgang, 1988-1999 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Sacks, Oliver, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Saenz-Badillos, Angel, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Sagan, Carl, 1977-1994 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      Undated photographs and negatives included. One description of a slide of negatives
    - Sagan, Carl, 1995-2001 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      Includes book by Jeremy Byman (2001). Undated photographs and negatives included
    - Sagen, Rose, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Sahn, David, 1993-2003 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Sakai, Naoki, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Salek, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Salino, Peter, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Sally, David, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Saloff-Coate, Laurent, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Salpeter, Edwin E., 1968-1997 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      One photograph undated. Negatives and a newspaper article included
    - Salpeter, Miriam M., 1970-1993 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Saltzman, Mark, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Saltzman, Sid, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Salvatore, Nick, 1983-2003 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Sampson, Harvey, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Sanderson, James A., 1993 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Sanderson, John, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Sanjur, Diva, 1988-1997 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Sansalone, Mary, 1990-1998 (Box 10, Folder 71)
      Photocopy and undated negatives included
    - Sansted, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Sass, Steven, 1993-2001 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Satiago-Irizarry, Vilma, 1994-2003 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Saylor, John, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Scaglione, Anna, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Scarlett, Janet, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Scatterday, Mark, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Schafer, Mike, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Scharf, Avi Yoel, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Schelhas-Miller, Chrissie, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Schember, Helene, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Scheraga, Harold A., 1968-2001 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Scherer, Cliff, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Schloss, Randall, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Schnall, Steve, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Schneider, Bob, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Schneider, Fred, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Schoggen, Phil, Undated (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Schrank, Elliott, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Schruben, Lee, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Schukken, Ynte, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Schuler, Richard, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      Description of one sheet of negatives included
    - Schutte, Regina, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Schwab, Stuart, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Schwanger, Steven, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Schwartz, Dan, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Schwartz, David, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - Schwartz, Peter, 1993-1999 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - Scolnick, Edward, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - Scott, Donna, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Scott, Fredric W., 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Scott, Norman, 1992-1998 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Scott, Sears, Undated (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Searle, Shayle, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Seeley, Tom, 1986-2001 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Seidman, Lisa, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Selco, Helen, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Self, Jim, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Selman, Bart, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Seltzer, Mark, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Semino, Matthew, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Servetto, Sergio, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Settner, Adam, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Seward, James, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Seyfang, Georg, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Seyler, Charles, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Seymore, Sandy, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Seznec, Alain, 1983-1993 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Shacham-Diamond, Yosef, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Shanen Jr., Nelson, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Shalala, Donna E., Undated (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Shanmugasundaram, Jayavel, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Shapiro, Connie, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Shapleigh, Jim, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Sharp, Geoffrey, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - Sharp, Gillian, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Sharp, Lauriston, Undated (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - Sharpe, Cindy, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Shealy, Dick, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - Sheehan, Sheila, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Sheils, Cathy, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Shelton, Tony, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Shepard, Nancy, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Sherbon, John, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - Shere, Peter, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - Sherman, Paul, 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 137)
      Negatives and descriptions of some photos included
    - Sherry, John, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - Sheilds, Elson, 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - Shippy, Judy, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - Shirdon, Mohammed, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Shoemaker, Christine, 1993-2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Shoemaker, Robin, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Shoemaker, Stowe, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Shortall, Janet, 1997-2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Shue, Henry, 1999-2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Shuler, Michael, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Shure, Ken, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Siegel, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Siemer, Bill, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Sierra, Robert, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Signor, Pamela, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Siguaw, Judy, 1997-2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Silber, Joel, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Silbey, Joel H., 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Silcox, John, 1971-1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Silicano, John, 1989-1997 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Silver, Robert, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Simler, Ken, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Simmons, Alex, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Simmons, Tony, 1993-2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Simon, Dan, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Simon, Kosali, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Simpson, David, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Sipple, John, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Sirois, Jean, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Sirer, Gun, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Photocopy only
    - Sisler, Dan, 1980-1997 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Slocum, Don, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Slocum, George, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Slom, Michael, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Smart, Mary Ann, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Smidt, Seymour, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Smith, Anna Marie, 1999-2003 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Smith, Charles R., 1994-2001 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Smith, Dean, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Deanna, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Smith, Goldwin, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Jordan, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Smith, Kimberly, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Smith, Martha, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Smith, R. David, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Robert J., 1993 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Smith, Stewart, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Smithline, Harriet, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Snead, Ernestine "Tina", 1993 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Snedeker, Suzanne, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Snow, Vicki, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Sogah, Dotsevi, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Sokey, Avtar, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Sokol, Thomas, 1970-1987 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      Some photographs undated. One photograph description included
    - Solheim, Ragnhila, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Solomon, Brenda, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Somma, Marie, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Sorrells, Mark, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Soyla, Asuman, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Sparrow, Rebecca, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Speight, W. Evan, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Spelke, Elizabeth, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Spencer, Michael, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Spicer, Bruce, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Spillers, Hortense, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Spinella, Donna, 1992-1998 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Spiro, Mark, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Spivey-Knowlton, Michael, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Sprague, Jane, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Squyres, Steven, 1995-2002 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Stacey, Gordon, Undated (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Stage, Nancy, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Staley, Liz, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Stamp, Neal, 1970-1979 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Stanek, Danielle, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Stark, Christina, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Staubinger, Alix, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Staum, Jeremy, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Stayman, Doug, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Stein, Dennis, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Stein, Peter, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Stein, Stuart, 1970-1979 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Steinburg, Michael, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Steingraber, Sandra, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Stember, David, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Stephenson, Lane, Undated (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Stern, David, 1993-2002 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Stern, Peter, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Stevens, Betsy, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Stevens, Janet, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Stevens, Randy, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - Stewart, Charles T., 1997 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Stewart, Diane, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - Stewart, Donald, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - Stewart, Harry, 1990-2002 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Stewart, Jack, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Stewart, Mary Jo, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Stewart, Patricia Carry, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - Stinson, Cornell, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Stinson, Harry, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Stipanwk, David, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - Stivers, Lee, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - St. Leger, Dr., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Stodghill, Paul, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Stokker, Laura, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Stolov, Susan, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - Stover, Patrick, 1994-2002 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - Strauss, Barry, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 104)
    - Strassberg, Richard, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Strausser, Pam, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - Street, Lloyd, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - Streeter, Deb, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - Streett, Bill, 1990-1994 (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - Strodel, Joseph, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - Strogatz, Steven, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - Strong, Norman, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - Strout, S. Cushing, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - Strupp, Barbara, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 114)
      Undated negatives, photograph, and photocopy included
    - Stuart, Chris, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - Stucky, Steven, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - Stundtner, Bob, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Sturm, Nancy, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Sturman, Michael, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - Sturmfelds, Bern, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Stycos, Joseph M., 1980-1989 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Stycos, Maria, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - Sullivan, Robert, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - Sultar, Jeff, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Summers, Mary, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Summers, Robert, 1990-2001 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Surisher, Raymond, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Susskind, Alex, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Sutliff, Donna, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Sutcliffe, Scott, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - Sutphin, Dean, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Suttom, Ozell, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Suzuki, Yuri, 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 133)
      Negatives only, one set of negatives undated
    - Svetsova, Lilia, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Swaminathan, Bhaskaran, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Swanson, Josephine, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Sweet, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Sweet, Stephen, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Swieriga, Robert, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Sykes, Allen, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - Szafara, Kristina, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Szasz, Susan, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Szebenyi, Tom, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - Szekely, Bea, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Takags, David, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Talber, Maurice, Undated (Box 11, Folder 146)
      Undated negative only